Ye Juncheng,
يي جونتشنغ ،
when can we get there?
متى نصل الى هناك
How do I know?
كيف أعرف؟
Can't you read?
ألا تستطيع القراءة؟
(2012, Star & Moon Lake) This map was made in 2012.
(2012، Star & Moon Lake) تم عمل هذه الخريطة في عام 2012.
Ten years ago.
قبل عشر سنوات.
Maps are similar, aren't they?
الخرائط متشابهة ، أليس كذلك؟
I found this map at home.
لقد وجدت هذه الخريطة في المنزل.
So, I didn't want to spend five yuan on a new one.
لذا ، لم أرغب في إنفاق خمسة يوانات على واحدة جديدة.
Ye Juncheng,
يي جونتشنغ ،
what a miser you are!
يا لك من بخيل!
Su Ziying, are you or are you not going to find the Star & Moon Lake?
Su Ziying ، هل أنت أو لن تجد بحيرة النجوم والقمر؟
I'm not the one who wants to see it.
أنا لست الشخص الذي يريد رؤيته.
Su Ziying, hurry.
سو تسى يينغ ، على عجل.
Ouch.
أوتش.
=My Honey=
= حبيبي =
=EP11 Love with One Kiss=
= EP11 الحب مع قبلة واحدة =
=EP11 Love with Two Kisses=
= EP11 الحب مع قبلتين =
Lin Han.
لين هان.
Mm?
مم؟
I have something to tell you.
لدي شيء لأخبرك به.
You sound terrifying.
يبدو أنك مرعب.
Don't be so serious, will you?
لا تكن جادًا جدًا ، أليس كذلك؟
Be serious.
كن جادا.
Think about it.
فكر في الأمر.
Why did Ye Juncheng take Su Ziying here?
لماذا أخذت يي جونتشنغ Su Ziying هنا؟
He...
هو...
He likes Su Ziying
يحب Su Ziying
and he's up to something.
وهو يخطط لشيء ما.
Then why are you here?
ثم لماذا أنت هنا؟
To protect Su Ziying.
لحماية Su Ziying.
Then why am I here?
إذن لماذا أنا هنا؟
I don't know.
لا أعلم.
You have to know.
يجب أن تعلم.
Why do I always follow Su Ziying?
لماذا أتبع Su Ziying دائمًا؟
Why do I keep hanging out with you two?
لماذا أستمر في التسكع معكما؟
And why did I come all the way to this place?
ولماذا أتيت إلى هذا المكان؟
Do you...
هل أنت...
Do you also like Su Ziying?
هل تحب Su Ziying أيضا؟
Lin Han, you idiot.
لين هان ، أيها الأحمق.
Come on.
هيا.
You can't be adoring the arrogant Ye Juncheng, can you?
لا يمكنك أن تعشق المتكبر يي جونتشنغ ، أليس كذلك؟
He's so annoying.
إنه مزعج للغاية.
Su Ziying doesn't like him.
سو زيينغ لا يحبه.
But he keeps...
لكنه يحتفظ ...
How thrilling!
كم هو مثير!
Are you all right?
هل انت بخير؟
Yes.
نعم.
What were you catching? The void?
ماذا كنت تصطاد؟  الفراغ؟
I didn't expect you to come down so quickly.
لم أتوقع منك أن تنزل بهذه السرعة.
And...
و...
If I touch you again,
إذا لمسك مرة أخرى ،
you'll slap me.
سوف تصفعني.
I think you failed to catch me deliberately.
أعتقد أنك فشلت في الإمساك بي عمدا.
Stop pretending,
كف عن التظاهر،
or it'll get back to you.
أو ستعود إليك.
Find the way quickly.
اعثر على الطريق بسرعة.
I twisted my ankle.
لقد لويت كاحلى.
It just got back to you.
لقد عاد إليك للتو.
I twisted it when I was trying to catch you.
لقد لفتها عندما كنت أحاول الإمساك بك.
What are you staring at me for?
لماذا تحدق بي؟
I'm not strong enough to carry you.
أنا لست قويًا بما يكفي لأحملك.
I can't walk, anyway.
لا أستطيع المشي على أي حال.
How about you go without me?
ماذا لو ذهبت بدوني؟
Let me stay alone
دعني أبقى لوحدي
in the wilderness
في البرية
to rot.
يتعفن.
Su Ziying,
سو تسي يينغ ،
you're really leaving?
انت حقا راحل؟
How heartless you are!
كم أنت قاسي القلب!
Hey, Su Ziying.
مرحبًا ، Su Ziying.
Slow down.
ابطئ.
So, this is the Star & Moon Lake?
إذن ، هذه هي بحيرة النجم والقمر؟
Come on.
هيا.
Only the moon
فقط القمر
and the bulbs...
والمصابيح ...
Why can it be called Star & Moon?
لماذا يطلق عليه Star & Moon؟
What a waste of time!
يا لها من مضيعة للوقت!
Let's get back.
دعونا نعود.
Hey, wait.
مهلا انتظر.
Look over there.
انظري هناك.
What just happened...
ماذا حدث للتو...
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
Okay, that's good.
حسنا هذا جيد.
Shall I not forget it, then?
ألا أنساها إذن؟
Lin Han,
لين هان ،
I'm a hothead.
أنا متهور.
I have to tell you something.
علي أن أخبرك بشيء.
I adore you
أنا أعشقك
and I'm up to something.
وأنا على وشك شيء.
I'm afraid you would be taken by some other girl
أخشى أن تأخذك فتاة أخرى
if I didn't tell you earlier.
إذا لم أخبرك سابقًا.
I'm done.
أنا انتهيت.
It's your turn to say something.
حان دورك لتقول شيئًا ما.
What should I say?
ماذا يجب أن أقول؟
According to idol dramas,
وفقا لدراما المعبود ،
you should say,
يجب عليك القول،
“Be my girlfriend.”
"كوني حبيبتي."
Fireflies?
اليراعات؟
So, fireflies are the stars.
لذا ، اليراعات هي النجوم.
But fireflies in winter?
لكن اليراعات في الشتاء؟
They're Divine Fireflies, I guess.
إنها اليراعات الإلهية ، على ما أعتقد.
They fly in the mountains in winter.
يطيرون في الجبال في الشتاء.
They still glow even when it is below six degrees centigrade.
لا تزال تتوهج حتى عندما تكون درجة الحرارة أقل من ست درجات مئوية.
They look so beautiful.
تبدو جميلة جدا.
They don't fly in winter to look beautiful,
لا يطيرون في الشتاء لتبدو جميلة ،
but for mat...
لكن للحصيرة ...
For communicating
للتواصل
and reproducing.
والتكاثر.
It's animal instinct.
إنها غريزة الحيوان.
Su Ziying, don't be a buzzkill, okay?
Su Ziying، don't be buzzkill، okay؟
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
♪Memories are fading♪
الذكريات تتلاشى
♪Sweetness peels off the past♪
حلاوة تقشر من الماضي ♪
♪A mess is left behind♪
خلفك فوضى
♪Who can't live without another♪
♪ من لا يستطيع العيش بدون آخر ♪
(Rough but sexy love confession)
(اعتراف حب قاسي ولكنه مثير)
♪Nothing is left but a heartbroken and lonely me♪
لم يبقَ سوى حزني وحيدا
♪My palms are no longer warm♪
راحتي لم تعد دافئة
You...
أنت...
Is your skin-to-skin heterophobia cured?
هل تم علاج رهاب الجلد للجلد الخاص بك؟
♪You're the one I can't talk about♪
♪ أنت الشخص الذي لا يمكنني التحدث عنه ♪
♪If♪
♪ إذا
Ye Juncheng...
يي جونتشنغ ...
♪The stubbornness returns♪
يعود العناد ♪
It's just delayed.
لقد تأخر فقط.
♪Let's get back together♪
♪ دعنا نعود معا ♪
♪You and I don't understand until we break up♪
♪ أنت وأنا لا نفهم حتى ننفصل ♪
♪Suffering impresses more than hearing♪
المعاناة تنال إعجاب أكثر من السمع ♪
♪What happened repeats in my mind making me no longer happy♪
♪ ما حدث يتكرر في ذهني يجعلني لم أعد سعيدا ♪
(All rights of network communication reserved by Tencent)
(جميع حقوق اتصالات الشبكة محفوظة لشركة Tencent)